skalezDgreat

Resume



ABOUT ME

I'm a blockchain smart contract engineer with a passion for innovation and collaboration. I excel in creating smart contracts, frontend applications, and specialize in community advisory and collaborative management.

I thrive on connecting with fellow developers and founders to push the boundaries of blockchain technology.

Blockchain(solidity)developer

Frontend(react)developer

DeFi researcher

EXPERIENCE

2022-2023
BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, OPHIRINSTITUTE
2022-2023
BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, AiYuki Nft
2022-2023
PARTNER, SparkFi

I built a portfolio tracker for the arbitrum blockchain https://horizon-swap.vercel.app/

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2023
AGNEEPATH
2023
OPHIRINSTITUTE
2023
SparkFi
2023
AiYuki
2022
LearnWeb3Dao

Dapp university

2022

CONTACT INFORMATION

Whatsapp: +234(0)8066042647

Email: holumacbeth@gmail.com

Discord username: skalez.sol or Skalez#0171

Twitter: @skalezDgreat

Telegram: @skalezDgreat

github: https://github.com/skalez-a